<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>misc on a neuro[log]</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/categories/misc/</link><description>Recent content in misc on a neuro[log]</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 06:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.neurolog.dev/categories/misc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Social Media Annoyances</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/social-media-annoyances/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 06:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/social-media-annoyances/</guid><description>Facebook is trying to get my attention I haven&amp;rsquo;t been on social media in years.
Apart from the odd post once every 4-6 months (at the most), I haven&amp;rsquo;t posted at all on Facebook - let alone Instagram, LinkedIn, or any other venue. But Facebook and Instagram keep bugging me for my attention. Notification after notification come up on my iPad and iPhone telling me that &amp;ldquo;Person&amp;rdquo; reacted to a a post you haven&amp;rsquo;t yet commented on.</description></item><item><title>Early Spring Cleaning</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/early-spring-cleaning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 06:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/early-spring-cleaning/</guid><description>Time to Get Shit DoneTM It&amp;rsquo;s time for an early spring cleaning.
I know, it&amp;rsquo;s only February, but I have to Get Shit DoneTM I&amp;rsquo;m going to try Trademarking that at some point. &amp;ldquo;Getting Things Done&amp;rdquo; is too lackadaisical to mean that you&amp;rsquo;re getting serious, in my opinion - with all due respect to David Allen. &amp;ldquo;Things&amp;rdquo; just doesn&amp;rsquo;t convey the necessity of some tasks which have to get done for me in my life at this point.</description></item><item><title>Old People and Phones</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/old-people-calls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 06:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/old-people-calls/</guid><description>Old people and phones Somebody really needs to start a global program to teach old people that the one thing they should never do is hold their telephone up to their ear when a person video calls them. It&amp;rsquo;s become a moral imperative to stop this sort of thing.
Really.</description></item><item><title>Happy 2024 and more</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/happy-2024-and-more/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 06:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/happy-2024-and-more/</guid><description>Happy New Year I haven&amp;rsquo;t written here in donkey&amp;rsquo;s years. Again. It&amp;rsquo;s hard to find inspiration to write when the world has just gone to shit since such a very long time. Additionally, I&amp;rsquo;ve pretty much made my feelings on a host of subjects known for decades. I hate being repetitive. I loathe listening to repetition, and I revile having to sound like a parrot.
WIth that said, I&amp;rsquo;ve recently felt the need to start writing and blogging again.</description></item><item><title>What were the 70s...</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/what-were-the-70s-like/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 07:40:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/what-were-the-70s-like/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;What were the 70s and early 80s really like?&amp;rdquo; They were dark, very contrasty, and grainy with lots of muted colours.</description></item><item><title>Nintendo Egg Game</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/egg-game/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/egg-game/</guid><description>A blast from the past I was cleaning out some more things today and I found this gem. It&amp;rsquo;s from the early 80s and I must have spent countless hours with my brother and even my parents playing this little game.
I looked online and they actually sell for quite a bit of money so I may actually end up selling it. I honestly have no intention of ever playing it again, but it was nice to see it again and yes, it does work.</description></item><item><title>Goodbye old MacBook Pro</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/goodbye-old-macbook-pro/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 08:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/goodbye-old-macbook-pro/</guid><description>Goodbye Old 2011 MacBook Pro. Yes, another &amp;ldquo;Goodbye&amp;rdquo; post from me - in so short a time. But this one is a must. I got this wonderful machine back in December 2011 and it&amp;rsquo;s been with me in Israel, Japan, the UK, and France. It was a workhorse for a very long time. But two and a half years ago I stopped using it in favour of the newer MacBook Pro I had for two years before getting my current one.</description></item><item><title>Goodbye Morning Bears</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/goodbye-morning-bears/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/goodbye-morning-bears/</guid><description>Goodbye morning bears. I&amp;rsquo;ve been posting a picture of a polar bear every single morning on Facebook since something like 2014 or 2015, without fail. And, as much as I love polar bears, I think it&amp;rsquo;s time to say goodbye to this morning tradition.
I started it because I wanted to see something happy first thing in the morning before anything else. But it has long since worn out that usefulness for me.</description></item><item><title>Second Post</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/second-post/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 16:30:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/second-post/</guid><description>Working on the template Now I have to customise this template a little more. I think I like this static site thing. It&amp;rsquo;s much less heavy than Wix or Wordpress.
Maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll turn this into a micro-blogging site as well. Not sure yet.</description></item><item><title>First Post</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/first-post/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 16:20:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/first-post/</guid><description>Welcome to my new blog. I just deployed it. It&amp;rsquo;s ready to go.
I&amp;rsquo;m doing this because I have some things to say. And I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to say them. In public.
It&amp;rsquo;s a brave step.</description></item></channel></rss>