<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>app on a neuro[log]</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/tags/app/</link><description>Recent content in app on a neuro[log]</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.neurolog.dev/tags/app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Warp.dev</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/warp-dev/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/warp-dev/</guid><description>warp terminal I&amp;rsquo;ve recently come across warp - a new terminal application currently for Mac only and in beta. Apparently they are working on a Linux and Windows release as well.
It&amp;rsquo;s pretty fantastic. It&amp;rsquo;s incredibly fast and very modern, written in Rust, and can do things no other terminal can do that I&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen.
As a long time user of iTerm, it includes some functions which iTerm currently does not have.</description></item><item><title>xbar</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/xbar/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/xbar/</guid><description>xbar is really cool. Recently, I found a very, very useful app for the Mac called xbar. It&amp;rsquo;s free and incredibly powerful and community-driven. Here is the link: xbar.
What it does is it puts a litle thing in your menu bar up top where you can load an enormous amount of plugins. These are written by all sorts of other people and fully open source. You have to figure out a little bit of code, like where your own directories are etc&amp;hellip; but you can install these plugins, edit them to fit your needs (the code is fully public so there won&amp;rsquo;t be any hacking of your system), and make it do whatever you want it to do.</description></item></channel></rss>