<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>tech on a neuro[log]</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/tags/tech/</link><description>Recent content in tech on a neuro[log]</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 06:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.neurolog.dev/tags/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Org-Mode does it all</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/org-does-it-all/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 06:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/org-does-it-all/</guid><description>Org really does it all Someone on Hacker News posted a link yesterday to a productivity directory of apps for, of all things, productivity.
It&amp;rsquo;s a nice enough website presenting apps such as Things, Evernote, Toggl, etc&amp;hellip; Naturally, however, I&amp;rsquo;m (once again) hit by the realisation that Org Mode (and Emacs) literally does all of this in one &amp;ldquo;package&amp;rdquo;, so to speak. It&amp;rsquo;s fairly impressive when you think about it, just how powerful it all is.</description></item><item><title>Social Media Annoyances</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/social-media-annoyances/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 06:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/social-media-annoyances/</guid><description>Facebook is trying to get my attention I haven&amp;rsquo;t been on social media in years.
Apart from the odd post once every 4-6 months (at the most), I haven&amp;rsquo;t posted at all on Facebook - let alone Instagram, LinkedIn, or any other venue. But Facebook and Instagram keep bugging me for my attention. Notification after notification come up on my iPad and iPhone telling me that &amp;ldquo;Person&amp;rdquo; reacted to a a post you haven&amp;rsquo;t yet commented on.</description></item><item><title>Old People and Phones</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/old-people-calls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 06:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/old-people-calls/</guid><description>Old people and phones Somebody really needs to start a global program to teach old people that the one thing they should never do is hold their telephone up to their ear when a person video calls them. It&amp;rsquo;s become a moral imperative to stop this sort of thing.
Really.</description></item><item><title>New Mastodon - Qoto.org</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/new-mastodon-qoto/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/new-mastodon-qoto/</guid><description>New Mastodon I migrated from the Mastodon server emacs.ch to qoto.org.
I still love emacs.ch but qoto has some more benefits, such as a 65,535 char post limit and a few other things. That&amp;rsquo;s huge. That&amp;rsquo;s enormous, in fact. It&amp;rsquo;s also a STEM-based instance, so there&amp;rsquo;s still some interesting things going on. So my new Mastodon is @natharari@qoto.org.
Also: I really ought to update this blog more often. I don&amp;rsquo;t know why I don&amp;rsquo;t.</description></item><item><title>Computer Literacy</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/computer-literacy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/computer-literacy/</guid><description>Computer Literacy I&amp;rsquo;m going to say something completely impolitic, but I don&amp;rsquo;t really care at this point about appearances:
I just have the feeling that most people are too stupid to actually figure out how easy #Mastodon is to use because of:
Choice and Unfamiliarity I remember when the internet was in its heyday (I was on it back in 1989 actually - but that&amp;rsquo;s another story) and we had such high hopes for humanity learning, growing, and communicating together.</description></item></channel></rss>