<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>emacs on a neuro[log]</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/tags/emacs/</link><description>Recent content in emacs on a neuro[log]</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 06:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.neurolog.dev/tags/emacs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Org-Mode does it all</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/org-does-it-all/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 06:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/org-does-it-all/</guid><description>Org really does it all Someone on Hacker News posted a link yesterday to a productivity directory of apps for, of all things, productivity.
It&amp;rsquo;s a nice enough website presenting apps such as Things, Evernote, Toggl, etc&amp;hellip; Naturally, however, I&amp;rsquo;m (once again) hit by the realisation that Org Mode (and Emacs) literally does all of this in one &amp;ldquo;package&amp;rdquo;, so to speak. It&amp;rsquo;s fairly impressive when you think about it, just how powerful it all is.</description></item><item><title>Skyrim and Emacs</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/skyrim-and-emacs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/skyrim-and-emacs/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m absolutely loving my MacBook Pro M1 Max What amazes me is how fast it is. Before, on the Intel MacBook Pro, I used to run Skyrim (and Fallout 4 as well as some other games) in native Windows mode. So, basically, it was like I was booting up a PC. But I didn&amp;rsquo;t have real access to my Mac Desktop or apps or anything else. The M1 is so fast that it&amp;rsquo;s running Skyrim in Parallels, at a faster FPS and far more stable than it was in native mode (I have no idea why but I&amp;rsquo;m not complaining).</description></item><item><title>Dracula Theme</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/dracula-theme/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 16:20:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/dracula-theme/</guid><description>I really like Dracula Theme for Emacs. I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying the Dracula Theme for about a week or so and I really enjoy it. It&amp;rsquo;s colourful and beautiful. It&amp;rsquo;s going on my permanent rotation for dark themes. I rotate between light and dark ones (light in the morning, dark at night) every day but I only keep the ones which please me the best, so my list is rather small.</description></item><item><title>Hugo and Emacs</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/hugo-and-emacs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 23:30:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/hugo-and-emacs/</guid><description>I’m installing two Emacs packages which help with Hugo sites. I intend on publishing directly from Emacs without ever having to go to the CLI. Not that I don’t love the CLI - I do. I just want to be able to do everything directly from an Emacs interface. So far, i’m having a blast figuring this stuff out and reading the docs. Maybe there’s an IFTTT thing I can use to directly publish a link to Mastadon when I post.</description></item></channel></rss>