<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>politics on a neuro[log]</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/tags/politics/</link><description>Recent content in politics on a neuro[log]</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 09:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.neurolog.dev/tags/politics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>QAnon Idiots and Espionage</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/q-anon-idiots-and-espionage/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/q-anon-idiots-and-espionage/</guid><description>I wonder how the QAnon idiots are justifying what&amp;rsquo;s happened. After all: Isn&amp;rsquo;t Trump supposed to be the &amp;ldquo;real&amp;rdquo; President? If he was really in charge&amp;hellip;why would the FBI raid his &amp;ldquo;inner sanctum&amp;rdquo;? Why would he have a warrant for a search?
What I&amp;rsquo;m really wondering is: How much information that counters their stupid, cretinous, &amp;ldquo;world view&amp;rdquo; does it take to snap them out of it? Will they ever actually snap out of it or will it just be a gradual process of moving on to the &amp;ldquo;next thing&amp;rdquo;?</description></item><item><title>A Terrorist Party</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/a-terrorist-party/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/a-terrorist-party/</guid><description>The Republicans are a terrorist party. I want to be absolutely clear: I mean that the Republicans are a terrorist party in the exact same way as Hamas is a terrorist party in most democracies (including the United States).
This is a political party which supported, and still supports, political violence to overthrow the democratically elected government of the United States - and a good chunk of which wants to install a theocratic government in its stead.</description></item><item><title>The FBI Raid on Trump</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/the-fbi-raid-on-trump/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/the-fbi-raid-on-trump/</guid><description>Don&amp;rsquo;t celebrate yet. With the recent FBI raid on Trump&amp;rsquo;s home, I&amp;rsquo;ve seen some people celebrating as if it&amp;rsquo;s all coming to a head. I think it&amp;rsquo;s worth stepping back for a moment to realize that we should be unconvinced of any progress to put Trump in jail until such time as he&amp;rsquo;s actually in jail.
The fact is that I cannot, for the life of me, see Trump ever going to jail.</description></item></channel></rss>