<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>tech on a neuro[log]</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/categories/tech/</link><description>Recent content in tech on a neuro[log]</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 06:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.neurolog.dev/categories/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Org-Mode does it all</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/org-does-it-all/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 06:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/org-does-it-all/</guid><description>Org really does it all Someone on Hacker News posted a link yesterday to a productivity directory of apps for, of all things, productivity.
It&amp;rsquo;s a nice enough website presenting apps such as Things, Evernote, Toggl, etc&amp;hellip; Naturally, however, I&amp;rsquo;m (once again) hit by the realisation that Org Mode (and Emacs) literally does all of this in one &amp;ldquo;package&amp;rdquo;, so to speak. It&amp;rsquo;s fairly impressive when you think about it, just how powerful it all is.</description></item><item><title>Social Media Annoyances</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/social-media-annoyances/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 06:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/social-media-annoyances/</guid><description>Facebook is trying to get my attention I haven&amp;rsquo;t been on social media in years.
Apart from the odd post once every 4-6 months (at the most), I haven&amp;rsquo;t posted at all on Facebook - let alone Instagram, LinkedIn, or any other venue. But Facebook and Instagram keep bugging me for my attention. Notification after notification come up on my iPad and iPhone telling me that &amp;ldquo;Person&amp;rdquo; reacted to a a post you haven&amp;rsquo;t yet commented on.</description></item><item><title>Old People and Phones</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/old-people-calls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 06:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/old-people-calls/</guid><description>Old people and phones Somebody really needs to start a global program to teach old people that the one thing they should never do is hold their telephone up to their ear when a person video calls them. It&amp;rsquo;s become a moral imperative to stop this sort of thing.
Really.</description></item><item><title>ChatGPT Dungeons &amp; Dragons</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/chatgpt-dnd/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 07:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/chatgpt-dnd/</guid><description>ChatGPT Dungeons &amp;amp; Dragons As a fun little experiment last night, I had ChatGPT write out a little Dungeons and Dragons adventure. From what I learned: You can get ChatGPT to be really specific and detailed. There are a few tricks which my repeated attempts have taught me:
You have to be really specific and detailed in your query. You can make it a very long sentence. I&amp;rsquo;ll post mine below so that you can see.</description></item><item><title>New Mastodon - Qoto.org</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/new-mastodon-qoto/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/new-mastodon-qoto/</guid><description>New Mastodon I migrated from the Mastodon server emacs.ch to qoto.org.
I still love emacs.ch but qoto has some more benefits, such as a 65,535 char post limit and a few other things. That&amp;rsquo;s huge. That&amp;rsquo;s enormous, in fact. It&amp;rsquo;s also a STEM-based instance, so there&amp;rsquo;s still some interesting things going on. So my new Mastodon is @natharari@qoto.org.
Also: I really ought to update this blog more often. I don&amp;rsquo;t know why I don&amp;rsquo;t.</description></item><item><title>Computer Literacy</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/computer-literacy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/computer-literacy/</guid><description>Computer Literacy I&amp;rsquo;m going to say something completely impolitic, but I don&amp;rsquo;t really care at this point about appearances:
I just have the feeling that most people are too stupid to actually figure out how easy #Mastodon is to use because of:
Choice and Unfamiliarity I remember when the internet was in its heyday (I was on it back in 1989 actually - but that&amp;rsquo;s another story) and we had such high hopes for humanity learning, growing, and communicating together.</description></item><item><title>Mastodon</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/mastodon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/mastodon/</guid><description>Mastodon I&amp;rsquo;m on Mastodon (links above) at Counter Social, and more and more at @natharari@emacs.ch. I&amp;rsquo;m going to delete my Twitter soon or deactivate it if possible, as I have no confidence in that medium whatsoever. More and more people are leaving and I&amp;rsquo;m happy to say that I&amp;rsquo;m one of them. Even though I didn&amp;rsquo;t use the site for the last few years, I just want no part of that disaster area.</description></item><item><title>Warp.dev</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/warp-dev/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/warp-dev/</guid><description>warp terminal I&amp;rsquo;ve recently come across warp - a new terminal application currently for Mac only and in beta. Apparently they are working on a Linux and Windows release as well.
It&amp;rsquo;s pretty fantastic. It&amp;rsquo;s incredibly fast and very modern, written in Rust, and can do things no other terminal can do that I&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen.
As a long time user of iTerm, it includes some functions which iTerm currently does not have.</description></item><item><title>Added Comments</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/added-comments/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/added-comments/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve added comments. In the extremely unlikely occurrence that anyone would ever comment on my site, I&amp;rsquo;ve added comments from Disqus. It was one of those little todo tasks on one of my org-mode lists I just had to get done. So there. I did it.</description></item><item><title>Skyrim and Emacs</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/skyrim-and-emacs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/skyrim-and-emacs/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m absolutely loving my MacBook Pro M1 Max What amazes me is how fast it is. Before, on the Intel MacBook Pro, I used to run Skyrim (and Fallout 4 as well as some other games) in native Windows mode. So, basically, it was like I was booting up a PC. But I didn&amp;rsquo;t have real access to my Mac Desktop or apps or anything else. The M1 is so fast that it&amp;rsquo;s running Skyrim in Parallels, at a faster FPS and far more stable than it was in native mode (I have no idea why but I&amp;rsquo;m not complaining).</description></item><item><title>xbar</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/xbar/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/xbar/</guid><description>xbar is really cool. Recently, I found a very, very useful app for the Mac called xbar. It&amp;rsquo;s free and incredibly powerful and community-driven. Here is the link: xbar.
What it does is it puts a litle thing in your menu bar up top where you can load an enormous amount of plugins. These are written by all sorts of other people and fully open source. You have to figure out a little bit of code, like where your own directories are etc&amp;hellip; but you can install these plugins, edit them to fit your needs (the code is fully public so there won&amp;rsquo;t be any hacking of your system), and make it do whatever you want it to do.</description></item><item><title>Getting Up</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/getting-up/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/getting-up/</guid><description>Getting up and walking around and doing things is good for you. I bought an Apple Watch several months ago. It&amp;rsquo;s my first smart watch and I couldn&amp;rsquo;t be happier about it.
I did my research. I didn&amp;rsquo;t just buy it, and obviously I didn&amp;rsquo;t jump onto the bandwagon immediately after they first started coming out. It took years. I thought that it would be sort of useless for me to get one.</description></item><item><title>Dracula Theme</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/dracula-theme/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 16:20:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/dracula-theme/</guid><description>I really like Dracula Theme for Emacs. I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying the Dracula Theme for about a week or so and I really enjoy it. It&amp;rsquo;s colourful and beautiful. It&amp;rsquo;s going on my permanent rotation for dark themes. I rotate between light and dark ones (light in the morning, dark at night) every day but I only keep the ones which please me the best, so my list is rather small.</description></item><item><title>Apple Reminders vs. Org Agenda</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/reminders-vs-org-agenda/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/reminders-vs-org-agenda/</guid><description>I’ve decided a few things about Org Mode. Org mode is an amazing tool - probably the best planner/organizer/todo list/outiner/editor system there ever was and is. In fact, I know of non-coders who have learned Emacs just to be able to use org-mode. And learning Emacs is not for the faint of heart. But org-mode is that powerful that it entices people towards it who would never normally touch code with a ten foot pole.</description></item><item><title>Added About Page</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/added-about-page/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 21:32:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/added-about-page/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve added an About page. I&amp;rsquo;ve just added an &amp;ldquo;about&amp;rdquo; page on the top menu.
I know I haven&amp;rsquo;t written anything here yet of value, but it will come. I did write an absolute rant about Facebook yesterday but I have yet to post it because it is rather harsh. My intention is to finalize it and then post it to Facebook for everyone to see. But we&amp;rsquo;ll see if I really feel like yelling at all the blind sheep who continue to use that place.</description></item><item><title>Hugo and Emacs</title><link>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/hugo-and-emacs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 23:30:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.neurolog.dev/posts/hugo-and-emacs/</guid><description>I’m installing two Emacs packages which help with Hugo sites. I intend on publishing directly from Emacs without ever having to go to the CLI. Not that I don’t love the CLI - I do. I just want to be able to do everything directly from an Emacs interface. So far, i’m having a blast figuring this stuff out and reading the docs. Maybe there’s an IFTTT thing I can use to directly publish a link to Mastadon when I post.</description></item></channel></rss>